snooth.com 2016-11-25

# Snooth | Privacy

Last Updated: September 15, 2011

## Information Collection

For each registered user, we collect the consumer's screen name, e-mail address, IP address, country of residence, and zip code. The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor and used by us to contact users regarding their account. This information is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without user consent.

Unregistered users may use the portions of the Snooth site that do not require registration. The IP addresses of these users are stored.

## Cookies

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

## Information Sharing with Third Parties

Snooth will not sell, rent or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission, except as follows: Snooth will share your email address with its promotional partners for marketing purposes.

Snooth uses cookies to help manage online advertising. These may be served by us, our 3rd party advertisers, or their agent (i.e. Doubleclick or other ad service). These cookies enable the advertiser to recognize your specific Web browser, which in turn enables them to learn how many people have seen a certain specific advertisement, and how many have seen it more than once. We use this information to track which advertisements our users consider relevant.

With both cookies and Doubleclick's Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. The advertiser or Doubleclick may also aggregate this anonymous information with other anonymously gathered information for statistical purposes.

For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Snooth site, or individual business units owned by Snooth Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

From time to time, Snooth will update its privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

## Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

Registered users can review the personal information they provided to Snooth and make any desired changes to the information at any time by logging in to their account and editing the information on the account settings page. They can also close their account by contacting Snooth through the contact us page. Users may export their reviews and ratings data at any time using the tools provided by Snooth.

## Editorial Policy

The content of Snooth's emails is chosen completely at the discretion of the Snooth Editorial Team. No one can pay to change the opinions written in a Snooth email. Selling our editorial content would destroy the legitimacy, integrity, and fun of Snooth emails and would ruin the trust between Snooth and its users. On occasion we will send out "sponsored" emails on behalf of wine organizations that have something special to offer the Snooth community, these emails will be marked as sponsored.

## Email Opt Out

Registered users who have elected to receive Snooth's daily email about wine deals, winemaking regions, offers from Snooth about trusted affiliates, and more, can choose to opt-out at any time by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any daily email. Users can also opt out from Snooth's daily emails from the [Account](http://www.snooth.com/account/) section. Further questions or comments regarding privacy can be directed to [privacy@snooth.com](mailto:privacy@snooth.com).

## Questions or Comments

[Contact us](http://www.snooth.com/contact/).
